[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "David, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I'm great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Are things a little chipper, more chipper down there than they were after the first debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, we were very, very happy with the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "And that's got to worry you, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Not - it doesn't really worry me, Piers, because I saw a whole bunch of data off of that debate including other polls and focused groups and dial groups.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "These are huge sticks to beat you guys with, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, let me say a few things about that first, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Do you accept as the administration that there were failings here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, look, I think what the president said last night was very, very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Department"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Does he never see any request of that nature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Piers, there are -- I don't know, I think 270 installations around the country and all of those go into the security professionals at the State Department who make judgments based on their expertise as to what is done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Do you guys think that perhaps you should be focusing on more serious stuff than this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, I think the binders for women formulation was an awkward formulation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "It reminds everybody of the ever present danger of a rogue terrorist element in whatever guise they come, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Yes, we -- this is a reality we live in, not just in the New York City area, all over the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "``", "NN", "IN", "NN", "''", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Why shouldn't Candy Crowley have jumped in when she did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, clearly the phrase \"act of terror\" was in the speech that was given in the Rose Garden.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Crowley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "But he was clumsy, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Not to my mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "He should have phrased it a different way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Perhaps.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Is that the way you see it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, I don't this changes the momentum or the dynamics of the race at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "And are you getting very worried about what you are seeing in the polls, which is clear momentum now surging behind Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I don't think there is clear momentum surging behind Mitt Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What did you make of the debate last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, it's interesting, because the first question, I was pleased to see, came from a college student.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "So both candidates are way off the mark, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "And meanwhile, you have a huge missed opportunity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Who is going to win that, and who has the stronger position on foreign policy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "So, I think this is one of those ones where I actually view Mitt Romney as having the potential -- he's coming in I think a bit as the under dog, but has a really strong hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Not a bad resume, isn't it, on the old -- on the old ticket in the first term?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I think you have to do a lot more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Matt, very, very quickly, the youth view of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I'd say two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Who do you trust more, Romney or Obama on foreign policy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RBR", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "The average young person probably is for Barack Obama on foreign policy, because he ended the war and he has a clear record.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Nobody really wants to do anything about government control, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "It appears not at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Disappointed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Again, I wasn't really impressed by the answers, were you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2014"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Are you more likely to get one if Barack Obama or Mitt Romney wins, from what you heard last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "If Mitt Romney wins, he said I'll have a job by the time I graduate in 2014.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Did you believe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "What was your overview, by the time you look back on it, about how they answered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "I thought neither question during the debate was on point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rose Garden"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "He told me that the cause for delay between the Rose Garden announcement and the 14 day official terrorist announcement was because he wanted to be deliberate, that any action he took anywhere in the world, especially in the Middle East, could cause irreparable harm, and he wanted to act on true information, not misinformation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Nina, did they talk to you, the candidates, afterward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Yes, I spoke to Governor Romney and I spoke to President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Did either of them give you any glimmer of hope about gun control or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I was anxious to hear President Obama's reaction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Carol, did you get anything from either of them afterwards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Not so much Romney, he was not -- but President Obama came by, thanked me for the question, and said it was a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Jeremy, either of them personally say, look, you can come and work for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I talked a little bit with Barack Obama's campaign people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "So is it quality time then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I guess so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121017pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "I haven't completely made my mind up, but I lean towards President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "ORGAN: President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}]